let easysubtractionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 19 - 8",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 - 7",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 - 10",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "4",
        AnswerD: "5",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 - 13",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 41 - 17",
        AnswerA: "23",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "25",
        AnswerD: "26",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 22 - 15",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 37 - 11",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "26",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 - 8",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 - 19",
        AnswerA: "19",
        AnswerB: "20",
        AnswerC: "21",
        AnswerD: "22",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 - 17",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 46 - 17",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "29",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 36 - 15",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "21",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 - 19",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 - 23",
        AnswerA: "15",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "15",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 34 - 16",
        AnswerA: "15",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 28 - 7",
        AnswerA: "20",
        AnswerB: "21",
        AnswerC: "22",
        AnswerD: "23",
        correctAnswer: "21",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 39 - 22",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 44 - 22",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "23",
        AnswerC: "24",
        AnswerD: "25",
        correctAnswer: "22",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 36 - 24",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 - 15",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 - 11",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "14",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 - 6",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 - 12",
        AnswerA: "4",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "7",
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 - 8",
        AnswerA: "19",
        AnswerB: "20",
        AnswerC: "21",
        AnswerD: "22",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 - 7",
        AnswerA: "9",
        AnswerB: "10",
        AnswerC: "11",
        AnswerD: "12",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 - 13",
        AnswerA: "13",
        AnswerB: "14",
        AnswerC: "15",
        AnswerD: "16",
        correctAnswer: "14",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 43 - 12",
        AnswerA: "28",
        AnswerB: "29",
        AnswerC: "30",
        AnswerD: "31",
        correctAnswer: "31",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 49 - 13",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 46 - 7",
        AnswerA: "38",
        AnswerB: "39",
        AnswerC: "40",
        AnswerD: "41",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 49 - 6",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "43",
        AnswerC: "44",
        AnswerD: "45",
        correctAnswer: "43",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 45 - 19",
        AnswerA: "23",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "25",
        AnswerD: "26",
        correctAnswer: "26",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 47 - 9",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
]